export default [
  {
    "back": "Hydrogen",
    "front": "H"
  },
  {
    "back": "Helium",
    "front": "He"
  },
  {
    "back": "Lithium",
    "front": "Li"
  },
  {
    "back": "Beryllium",
    "front": "Be"
  },
  {
    "back": "Boron",
    "front": "B"
  },
  {
    "back": "Carbon",
    "front": "C"
  },
  {
    "back": "Nitrogen",
    "front": "N"
  },
  {
    "back": "Oxygen",
    "front": "O"
  },
  {
    "back": "Fluorine",
    "front": "F"
  },
  {
    "back": "Neon",
    "front": "Ne"
  },
  {
    "back": "Sodium",
    "front": "Na"
  },
  {
    "back": "Magnesium",
    "front": "Mg"
  },
  {
    "back": "Aluminum",
    "front": "Al"
  },
  {
    "back": "Silicon",
    "front": "Si"
  },
  {
    "back": "Phosphorus",
    "front": "P"
  },
  {
    "back": "Sulfur",
    "front": "S"
  },
  {
    "back": "Chlorine",
    "front": "Cl"
  },
  {
    "back": "Argon",
    "front": "Ar"
  },
  {
    "back": "Potassium",
    "front": "K"
  },
  {
    "back": "Calcium",
    "front": "Ca"
  },
  {
    "back": "Scandium",
    "front": "Sc"
  },
  {
    "back": "Titanium",
    "front": "Ti"
  },
  {
    "back": "Vanadium",
    "front": "V"
  },
  {
    "back": "Chromium",
    "front": "Cr"
  },
  {
    "back": "Manganese",
    "front": "Mn"
  },
  {
    "back": "Iron",
    "front": "Fe"
  },
  {
    "back": "Cobalt",
    "front": "Co"
  },
  {
    "back": "Nickel",
    "front": "Ni"
  },
  {
    "back": "Copper",
    "front": "Cu"
  },
  {
    "back": "Zinc",
    "front": "Zn"
  },
  {
    "back": "Gallium",
    "front": "Ga"
  },
  {
    "back": "Germanium",
    "front": "Ge"
  },
  {
    "back": "Arsenic",
    "front": "As"
  },
  {
    "back": "Selenium",
    "front": "Se"
  },
  {
    "back": "Bromine",
    "front": "Br"
  },
  {
    "back": "Krypton",
    "front": "Kr"
  },
  {
    "back": "Rubidium",
    "front": "Rb"
  },
  {
    "back": "Strontium",
    "front": "Sr"
  },
  {
    "back": "Yttrium",
    "front": "Y"
  },
  {
    "back": "Zirconium",
    "front": "Zr"
  },
  {
    "back": "Niobium",
    "front": "Nb"
  },
  {
    "back": "Molybdenum",
    "front": "Mo"
  },
  {
    "back": "Technetium",
    "front": "Tc"
  },
  {
    "back": "Ruthenium",
    "front": "Ru"
  },
  {
    "back": "Rhodium",
    "front": "Rh"
  },
  {
    "back": "Palladium",
    "front": "Pd"
  },
  {
    "back": "Silver",
    "front": "Ag"
  },
  {
    "back": "Cadmium",
    "front": "Cd"
  },
  {
    "back": "Indium",
    "front": "In"
  },
  {
    "back": "Tin",
    "front": "Sn"
  },
  {
    "back": "Antimony",
    "front": "Sb"
  },
  {
    "back": "Tellurium",
    "front": "Te"
  },
  {
    "back": "Iodine",
    "front": "I"
  },
  {
    "back": "Xenon",
    "front": "Xe"
  },
  {
    "back": "Cesium",
    "front": "Cs"
  },
  {
    "back": "Barium",
    "front": "Ba"
  },
  {
    "back": "Lanthanum",
    "front": "La"
  },
  {
    "back": "Cerium",
    "front": "Ce"
  },
  {
    "back": "Praseodymium",
    "front": "Pr"
  },
  {
    "back": "Neodymium",
    "front": "Nd"
  },
  {
    "back": "Promethium",
    "front": "Pm"
  },
  {
    "back": "Samarium",
    "front": "Sm"
  },
  {
    "back": "Europium",
    "front": "Eu"
  },
  {
    "back": "Gadolinium",
    "front": "Gd"
  },
  {
    "back": "Terbium",
    "front": "Tb"
  },
  {
    "back": "Dysprosium",
    "front": "Dy"
  },
  {
    "back": "Holmium",
    "front": "Ho"
  },
  {
    "back": "Erbium",
    "front": "Er"
  },
  {
    "back": "Thulium",
    "front": "Tm"
  },
  {
    "back": "Ytterbium",
    "front": "Yb"
  },
  {
    "back": "Lutetium",
    "front": "Lu"
  },
  {
    "back": "Hafnium",
    "front": "Hf"
  },
  {
    "back": "Tantalum",
    "front": "Ta"
  },
  {
    "back": "Wolfram",
    "front": "W"
  },
  {
    "back": "Rhenium",
    "front": "Re"
  },
  {
    "back": "Osmium",
    "front": "Os"
  },
  {
    "back": "Iridium",
    "front": "Ir"
  },
  {
    "back": "Platinum",
    "front": "Pt"
  },
  {
    "back": "Gold",
    "front": "Au"
  },
  {
    "back": "Mercury",
    "front": "Hg"
  },
  {
    "back": "Thallium",
    "front": "Tl"
  },
  {
    "back": "Lead",
    "front": "Pb"
  },
  {
    "back": "Bismuth",
    "front": "Bi"
  },
  {
    "back": "Polonium",
    "front": "Po"
  },
  {
    "back": "Astatine",
    "front": "At"
  },
  {
    "back": "Radon",
    "front": "Rn"
  },
  {
    "back": "Francium",
    "front": "Fr"
  },
  {
    "back": "Radium",
    "front": "Ra"
  },
  {
    "back": "Actinium",
    "front": "Ac"
  },
  {
    "back": "Thorium",
    "front": "Th"
  },
  {
    "back": "Protactinium",
    "front": "Pa"
  },
  {
    "back": "Uranium",
    "front": "U"
  },
  {
    "back": "Neptunium",
    "front": "Np"
  },
  {
    "back": "Plutonium",
    "front": "Pu"
  },
  {
    "back": "Americium",
    "front": "Am"
  },
  {
    "back": "Curium",
    "front": "Cm"
  },
  {
    "back": "Berkelium",
    "front": "Bk"
  },
  {
    "back": "Californium",
    "front": "Cf"
  },
  {
    "back": "Einsteinium",
    "front": "Es"
  },
  {
    "back": "Fermium",
    "front": "Fm"
  },
  {
    "back": "Mendelevium",
    "front": "Md"
  },
  {
    "back": "Nobelium",
    "front": "No"
  },
  {
    "back": "Lawrencium",
    "front": "Lr"
  },
  {
    "back": "Rutherfordium",
    "front": "Rf"
  },
  {
    "back": "Dubnium",
    "front": "Db"
  },
  {
    "back": "Seaborgium",
    "front": "Sg"
  },
  {
    "back": "Bohrium",
    "front": "Bh"
  },
  {
    "back": "Hassium",
    "front": "Hs"
  },
  {
    "back": "Meitnerium",
    "front": "Mt"
  },
  {
    "back": "Darmstadtium",
    "front": "Ds"
  },
  {
    "back": "Roentgenium",
    "front": "Rg"
  },
  {
    "back": "Copernicium",
    "front": "Cn"
  },
  {
    "back": "Nihonium",
    "front": "Nh"
  },
  {
    "back": "Flerovium",
    "front": "Fl"
  },
  {
    "back": "Moscovium",
    "front": "Mc"
  },
  {
    "back": "Livermorium",
    "front": "Lv"
  },
  {
    "back": "Tennessine",
    "front": "Ts"
  },
  {
    "back": "Oganesson",
    "front": "Og"
  }
]